<?xml version="1.1" ?>
<root>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="1">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 1</TITLE>
            <BODY>What makes every American a typical one
                is a desire to get a well-paid job that will cover their credit card.
                A credit card is an indispensable part of life in America. In other words,
                any American knows that how he or she handles their credit card or cards,
                either will help them or haunt them for years.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="2">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 2</TITLE>
            <BODY>In the U.S. getting a card
                isn’t as hard as it used to be. Some companies now mail applications
                to high school students, rather than waiting for them to get into college.
                At their best credit cards allow their owners to reserve hotel rooms,
                rent cars and finance larger purchases over several months.
                At their worst, cards allow people with poor money management skills to get into a high-interest debt.
            </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="3">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 3</TITLE>
            <BODY>For those who are deep in credit card debt,
                there are some Credit Services agencies that offer
                anyone in America both online or telephone, and face-to-face counseling.
                The counselors may propose a debt management plan.
                The plan includes lower interest payments for clients and setting up a pay off timetable.
                The agencies’ average client makes about $32,000 a year and has more than $16,000 debt in the program.
                Usually the agencies charge zero up to $30 monthly to manage the debt service plan.
        </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="4">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 4</TITLE>
            <BODY>Credit Services counselors advise,
                that if an American gets divorced, he or she may eliminate all joint
                debts by paying them off or transferring debt into a one-name account.
                Even in happy marriages, the agency advises that the husband and wife
                should each have a credit card in their name only to establish separate credit histories.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="5">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 5</TITLE>
            <BODY>Once debts have been repaid,
                an American can re-establish his/her good credit by applying
                for a secured credit card and paying the balance off regularly.
                A store credit card usually is the next step, followed by applying
                for a major credit card such as a Visa or MasterCard.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="6">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 6</TITLE>
            <BODY>Advertising companies say
                advertising is necessary and important. It informs people about new products.
                Advertising hoardings in the street make our environment colourful.
                And adverts on TV are often funny. Sometimes they are mini-dramas
                and we wait for the next programme in the mini-drama. Advertising can educate, too.
                Adverts tell us about new, healthy products. And adverts in magazines give us ideas
                for how to look prettier, be fashionable and be successful.
                Without advertising life is boring and colourless.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="7">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 7</TITLE>
            <BODY>But some consumers argue that advertising is a bad thing.
                They say that advertising j bad for children.
                Adverts make children ‘pester’ their parents to buy things for them.
                Advertisers know we love our children and want to give them everything.
                So they use children’s ‘pester power’ to sell their products.
                Finally, consumers say, if there is advertising there must be rules.
                Some adverts advertise unhealthy things like cigarettes and make people waste their money.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="8">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 8</TITLE>
            <BODY>The other emerging trend for adults is gardening.
                People spend so much time at home.
                They find gardening a great way of relaxation and getting a sense of satisfaction.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="9">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 9</TITLE>
            <BODY>The recent interest in crafts in America is not only a matter of economics.
                It’s also a reflection of people’s new environmental sensibilities.
                The concepts of "reduce, reuse, and recycle" are the cornerstone of crafting.
                Pieces of fabric can be put together to make gorgeous quilting designs, and some types
                of waste can be composted and used as fertilizer in gardening.
                In this respect, Americans will say: "Save money and save the planet. It’s a winning combination!"
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="10">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 10</TITLE>
            <BODY>America’s music culture has been growing and spreading its popularity for many years.
                The best known American singers are those who sing to the rock beat.
                Rock revolutionized music in America in the early 1950s and nowadays, shows no sign of slowing down.
                There isn’t a corner of the globe that hasn’t felt the drive of American rock.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="11">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 11</TITLE>
            <BODY>Two other genres of American music have had a strong hold for the past decade.
                They are rap and hip hop. Born of inner-city poverty, rap replaces sung melodies,
                with rhythmically punchy recitation set to an African-American roots.
                However, they were quickly embraced by white performers.
                Today rappers appear in TV commercials, movies and various shows.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="12">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 12</TITLE>
            <BODY>A look around the pop scene will turn up the presence
                of "techno" music in nightclubs and new "garage bands".
                The Vines and The Strokes are among today’s examples of "garage bands" in the USA.
                Mainstream pop provides its typical lion’s share of entertainment.
                Along with female vocalists (Sheryl Crowe, Lucinda Williams, Jennifer Paige, etc.),
                "boy bands" (Backstreet Boys, Boys II Men and others) have performed their music since the 1990s.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="13">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 13</TITLE>
            <BODY>Due to a great number of radio stations, which play
                "the greatest hits of the ’80s, ’90s and today", older styles of pop continue to
                be a strong part of America’s music culture. Sounds from even earlier in rock history do not fade away.
                For instance, the group Sugar Ray combines so many elements from earlier rock styles,
                so that their music is at once nostalgic and refreshing.
                Norah Jones, a female singer who captured eight Grammy Awards in 2003,
                provides a direct link between the softer rock beat and communicative lyrics.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="14">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 14</TITLE>
            <BODY>As a wrap up America’s music
                culture does everything possible to unite in it not only people of different music genres,
                but of different generations, as well.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="15">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 15</TITLE>
            <BODY>Transform Logic Corp said it
                has revised downward its previously reported fourth quarter and
                year, ended October 31, results to reflect compensation expense
                for employee stock options.
                The company said resolution of this disagreement with its
                auditors came as a result of Securities and Exchange Commission
                involvement. The company will amend its option-granting
                procedure to conform to the SEC decision which will eliminate
                future charges, it added.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="16">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 16</TITLE>
            <BODY>New Year’s Day (January 1) — Americans
                celebrate the beginning of a new year at home,
                with friends, and in gatherings from the Tournament of Roses Parade in California
                to the giant gathering in New York’s Times Square.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="17">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 17</TITLE>
            <BODY>Christmas Day (December 25) — Most Protestants and Roman Catholics
                and some Orthodox Christians celebrate the birth of Jesus on December 25.
                Christmas is celebrated at home, with the decoration and display of evergreen Christmas Trees,
                and with families and children exchanging gifts and cards.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="18">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 18</TITLE>
            <BODY>Labor Day (first Monday in September) — the Labor Day
                holiday commemorates the contributions of working men and women.
                For many Americans the holiday demarks the unofficial end of summer and beginning of the school year.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="19">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 19</TITLE>
            <BODY>There are a number of traditions for weddings that
                have survived into the 21st century. It is still traditional for the bride and groom
                to have their own parties the night before getting married.
                The groom’s party is called a ‘Stag party’, while the bride’s is known as a ‘Hen party’.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="20">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 20</TITLE>
            <BODY>On the morning of the wedding, the groom should not see the bride.
                If he does, this is bad luck. The bride puts on her special wedding dress, which is usually white.
                She also needs to wear ‘something old, something new, something borrowed and something blue’.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="21">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 21</TITLE>
            <BODY>Holiday Corp's Holiday Inn Hotel
                Group said it will add a record 17 hotels with 4,440 rooms to
                its international division as part of its plan to double its
                presence abroad by 1995.
                The company said its international division will reach
                50,000 rooms by this spring, classifying it as the eighth
                largest hotel chain in the world. Holiday said by the end of
                the year, there will be approximately 220 Holiday Inn hotels in
                54 countries.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>


    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="22">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 22</TITLE>
            <BODY>At the church, or registry office,
                the bride and groom exchange rings before walking together back down the aisle.
                When they get outside, the bride throws her bouquet in the air.
                Tradition says that whoever catches it will be the next person to get married.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="23">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 23</TITLE>
            <BODY>But it’s not only the bride who throws something.
                All the people at the wedding throw confetti and rice over the happy couple.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>
    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="24">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 24</TITLE>
            <BODY>One of the most alarming forms of air
                pollution is acid rain.
                It results from the release into the atmosphere of sulphur and nitrogen
                oxides that react with water droplets and return to earth in the form of acid rain, mist or snow.
                Acid rain is killing forests in Canada, the USA, and central and northern Europe.
                (Nearly every species of tree is affected.) It has acidified lakes and streams and they can’t
                support fish, wildlife, plants or insects.
                (In the USA 1 in 5 lakes suffer from this type of pollution).
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>


    <DOCUMENTS NEWID="25">

        <TEXT>
            <TITLE>Text 25</TITLE>
            <BODY>Par Pharmaceutical Inc said
                it has been cleared by New York Stock Exchange authorities to
                apply for NYSE listing and expected to be listed by April or
                May.
                The company's stock is now traded on the NASDAQ system.
                </BODY></TEXT>
    </DOCUMENTS>

</root>